Teri Stubs PUNK010
People's Archive, MLK Library
Teri Stubs Collection
1990-1993
People's Archive, MLK Library
Stubs, Teri
PUNK010
4 Boxes
Punk rock music
- Series 1
  - Jawbox, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Lucy Brown, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cop Shot Cop, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Holy Cow, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Clutch, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Jack Hammer, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Thud, 34096 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Thud, 34180 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Thud, 34032 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Ignition, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Executive Slacks, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Gwar, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Sonic Youth, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Cop shoot Cop, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Nine Inch Nails, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Scope and Contents
    Second show at club
  - Nine Inch Nails, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Fudge Tunnel, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Adolescents, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Lucy Brown, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Velocity girl, Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Strange Boutique, Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Seven Seconds, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - John Sex, Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Mud Honey, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Holy Cow, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Gumball, Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Royal Cresent Mob, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Jawbox, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Who is God, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Pain teens, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Killing Joke, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Clutch, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Clutch, Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Clutch, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Lucy Brown, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Thud, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Psychedelic Furs, Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Firehose, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Kingface, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Strange Boutique, Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Thud, Undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Thud, Undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Lucy Brown, Undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Marginal Man, Undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Jawbox, Undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Slickee Boys, Undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Fugazi, Undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - G.I., Undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - That Petrol Emotions, Undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Happy Go Licky, Undated (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Fugazi, Undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Fugazi, Undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Henry Rollins, Undated (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Psychedelic Furs, Undated (Box 4, Folder 47)